Guide to the Hanna House Collection SC0280
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Architectural drawings, 1936-1963
  - Addition to house for Dr. Hanna, floor plan initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd (Preliminary plan with handwritten note by Wright, Frank Lloyd re: extension into adjacent property), 1946 Sep 15; 83; 1 sepia transparency; 29 x 28 inches (Box Sb13)
  - Addition to house for Dr. Hanna, elevations, initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1946 Sep 15; 84; 1 blueprint; 29 x 28 inches (Box Sb13)
  - Floor plan, elevation and section of proposed addition, initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1946 Sep 15; 85; 1 blueprint; 29 x 28 inches (Box Sb13)
  - Roof plan showing the guest rooms, proposed addition, initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1946 Sep 15; 86; 1 blueprint; 29 x 28 inches (Box Sb13)
  - Plan of alterations, dated; (Prepared by Fred Langhorst, Architect), 1946 Oct 23; 88; 1 diazo print; 22 x 27 inches (Box Sa13)
    Langhorst, Fred
  - Section and detail of sash and wall alteration, dated; (Prepared by Fred Langhorst, Architect), 1946 Oct 23; 89; 1 diazo print; 24 x 35 inches (Box Sb13)
  - Sketch and plan of kitchen counter, alteration, dated; (Prepared by Fred Langhorst; contains pencilled revisions), 1946 Oct 23; 90; 1 diazo print; 20.5 x 25 inches (Box Sa13)
  - Addition and alterations to Honeycomb House.. .; (This is a subsequent, modified version of No. 91 [?]), 1948?; 93; 1 sepia transparency; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb11)
  - Addition and alterations to Honeycomb House.. ., showing details of organ alcove, undated; 94; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sa20)
  - Illumination plan - sheet 1, 1937 Mar 23; AD008; 1 pencil on paper (original)
    Wolf, Carl T., electrical engineer; Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959
  - Plan of mat and tunnel - sheet 2, 1937 Mar 23; AD009; 1 pencil on paper (original)
    Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959; Wolf, Carl T., electrical engineer
  - Floor plan and details for lighting and power - sheet 3, 1937 Mar 23; AD010; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Continuation of floor plan and details for lighting and power - Sheet 4, 1937 Mar 23; AD011; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Details and position of walls over typical floor unit; flush celing, light details; section through playroom & boys bedroom - Sheet 5, 1937 Mar 22; AD012; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Sanctum fireplace spit and fireplace tools, 1937; AD013; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Easy chair, ottoman, and floor cushions, 1937; AD014; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Straight chair; full size design for perforated boards, 1937; AD015; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Floor plan of Hanna House showing changes in bedrooms, 1955; AD016; 1 pencil on paper (original)
  - Revised floor plan of Hanna House showing change in terraces; dated and initialed by Wright, Frank Lloyd, illegible; 17; 1 blueprint; 24.5 x 42 inches (Box Sa18)
  - Sheet 1 - general plan: addition and alteration to house for Mr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna; initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1949 Dec 20; 95; 2 1 blueprint; 1 original; 36 x 40.5 inches (Box Sa20 Sb11)
  - Sheet 2 - elevations: additions and alterations to house for Mr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna; initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1949 Dec 20; 96; 2 1 blueprint; 1 original; 36 x 40.5 inches (Box Sa19 Sb11)
  - Sheet 3 - details & roof framing: addition and alterations to house for Mr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna; initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1949 Dec 20; 97; 2 1 blueprint; 1 original; 36 x 40.5 inches (Box Sa19 Sb11)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 1: foundation plan and details, post-contract revision, 1950 May 12, Mar 20; 99; 2 blackline diazo print; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa15 Sa19)
    Spencer & Ambrose
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 2: plan, elevations and sash schedule, post-contract revision (2 cc); blueprint, 1950 May 12, Mar 20; 100; 3 blackline diazo print; blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa17 Sa15 Sb13)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 3: roof framing plans, details and sections, post-contract revision; blueprint, 1950 May 12, Mar 20; 101; 2 blackline diazo print; blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa19)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 4: wall and sash details, post-contract revision; blueprint, 1950 May 12, Mar 20; 102; 2 blackline diazo print; blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sb11)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 5: shop fireplace details and interior elevations, revision, 1950 Apr 24; 103; 1 blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa16)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 6: plans of plumbing, heating and electrical work, post-contract revision; plus a copy (mislabelled Sheet 5), 1950 May 12, Mar 20; 104; 2 blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa20 Sb11)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 7: detail plan sash group 'A' as revised; post-contract, 1950 Apr 24, Aug 31; 105; 1 blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa20)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 8: plumbing detail plan and elevation, post-contract revision, 1950 Jul 24; 106; 1 blueprint; 30 x 42 inches (Box Sa20)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 9: plumbing riser diagram, 1950 Jun 13; 107; 1 blueprint; 11 x 19 inches (Box Sa13)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 10: extension of trellis motif in new storeroom, 1950 Jul 5; 108; 1 blueprint; 12 x 25 inches (Box Sa13)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 11: wall sections and plate plans and details, 1950 Jul 10; 109; 1 blueprint; 30 x 28 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 12: supplementary cross sections, 1950 Jul 18; 110; 1 blueprint; 30 x 28 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 13: plan of sash group A and new terrace at shop, 1950 Jul 26; 111; 1 blueprint; 30 x 22 inches (Box Sa13)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 14: plan of east truss over work bench, 1950 Oct 12; 112; 1 blueprint; 20.5 x 31 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet 15: plan of east soffit truss and full-size section facia at outer sash of new bay window, 1950 Oct 16; 113; 1 blueprint; 18 x 30 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet S-1: new wall at tree plant box, 1950 Apr 11; 114; 1 blueprint; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box Sa13)
  - Addition to the residence of Prof. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna - Sheet S-2: revised foundation section 3A, 1950 Apr 11; 115; 1 blueprint; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Sheet No. 1, Facias - Hanna Residence (millwork shop drawing), undated; 116; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 42 inches (Box Sa20)
    Pacific Manufacturing Co
  - Sheet No. 2, Material for frames, facia & boards & battens - Hanna Residence (millwork shop drawing), undated; 117; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 42 inches (Box Sa16)
  - Sheet No. 3, Jambs for sash & doors - Hanna Residence (millwork shop drawing), undated; 118; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 42 inches (Box Sa16)
  - Sheet No. 4, Ext. doors & sash - Hanna Residence (millwork shop drawing), undated; 119; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 42 inches (Box Sb11)
  - Sheet No. 5, Sash - Hanna Residence (millwork shop drawing), undated; 120; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 42 inches (Box Sb11)
  - Sheet No. 6, Full size details of sash - Hanna Residence (millwork shop drawing), undated; 121; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 42 inches
  - Floor plan of Hanna House showing change in bedrooms, initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1955; 122; 1 blueline diazo print; 21 x 33 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Hanna House changes in bedroom area, intialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1956 Jan 20, Jan 25; 123; 1 blueprint; 29 x 36 inches (Box Sb14)
    Preliminary plan of modications, with notes and modifications noted in white and black pencil.
  - Present structure - 1937; sketch by Jean Hanna, 1956; 124; 1 Pencil and crayon on tracing paper; 16 x 22 inches
    Hanna, Jean Shuman
  - Proposed plan; sketch by Jean Hanna, 1956; 125; 1 Pencil and crayon on tracing paper; 16 x 22 inches
  - Proposed plan with furniture, initialled JSH; sketch by Jean Hanna, 1956; 126; 1 Pencil and crayon on tracing paper; 16 x 22 inches (Box Sa12)
  - Untitled, undated partial floor plan by Jean Hanna, showing variations to No. 122, 1956; 127; 1 Pencil and crayon on tracing paper; 16 x 22 inches
  - Untitled, undated partial floor plan by Jean Hanna, similar to No. 122, 1956; 128; 1 Pencil and crayon on tracing paper; not given
  - Untitled, undated partial floor plan by Jean Hanna, 1956; 129; 1 Black and colored pencil on graph paper; 19 x 29 inches
  - Untitled partial floor plan, initialled by Jean Hanna, 1957 Feb 4; 130; 1 Blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches
  - Hanna House, partial floor plan by Jean Hanna, 1957 Feb 5; 131; 1 Blue and red pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches
  - Untitled, undated partial floor plan showing lighting and switch locations by Jean Hanna, 1957; 132; 1 Blue, red and black pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches (Box Sb17)
  - Untitled, undated partial floor plan showing lighting, power outlets and switch locations by Jean Hanna, 1957; 133; 1 Blue and black pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches (Box Sb17)
  - Sheet 1 - Plan: alterations for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, incl. outside elevations, initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1957 Feb; 134; 1 blueline diazo print; 26 x 36 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Sheet 1 - Plan: alterations for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna; (no. 130 [?134] with pencil notes and corrections by Jean Hanna), 135; 1 blueline diazo print; 26 x 36 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Sheet 2 - Details: alterations for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, incl. framing plan for flat roof and fireplace details; initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1957 Feb; 136; 1 blueline diazo print; 26 x 36 inches (Box Sb14)
  - Sheet 2 - Details: alterations for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 137; 1 blueline diazo print; 26 x 36 inches (Box Sb15)
  - Hanna House, partial floor plan based on No. 130, initialled JSH, 1957 Feb 19; 138; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing papers; 19 x 24 inches
  - Lighting - Hanna House; partial floor plan by Jean Hanna based on No. 130, 1957 Mar 1; 139; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches
  - Furniture detail, partial floor plan by Jean Hanna based on No. 130, initialled JSH, 1957 Mar 9; 140; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches (Box Sa12)
  - Lighting chart, partial floor plan by Jean Hanna based on No. 130, initialled JSH, 1957 Mar 9; 141; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches (Box Sb17)
  - Traffic lights, partial floor plan based on No. 130, initialled JSH, 1957 Mar 9; 142; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches (Box Sb17)
  - Reading lights, partial floor plan based on No. 130, initialled JSH, 1957 Mar 9; 143; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches (Box Sb17)
  - Utility outlets, partial floor plan based on No. 130, initialled JSH, 1957 Mar 9; 144; 1 Black and blue pencil on tracing paper; 19 x 24 inches
  - Undated partial plan of library by Jean Hanna, showing built-in furniture, 1957; 146; 1 Pencil on tracing paper; 11 x 8.5 inches (Box Sa12)
  - Galvanized metal box, 1957; 147; 1 Pencil on paper; 9 x 14 inches
  - Hanna, 1957; 148; 1 Pencil on paper; 11 x 14 inches
  - Plan - alterations for Mr. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 1957 Apr; 149; 2 blueline diazo print; 20 x 25 inches (Box Sa14)
    This revised plan incorporated the results of the various studies and refinements of Jean Hanna of the plan shown on No. 130, drated by Taliesin apprentice D.Dodge.
    Dodge, David
  - Plan - alterations for Mr. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna (No. 149 with pencilled dimensions.), 1957 Apr; 150; 1 blueline diazo print; 20 x 25 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Plan - alterations for Mr. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna (No. 149 with Building Dept. submitted), 1957 Apr 3; 151; 1 blueline diazo print; 20 x 25 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Plan - alterations for Mr. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna (No. 149 with red pencil notes by Aaron Green, architect.), 1957 Apr; 152; 1 blueline diazo print; 20 x 25 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Plan - alterations for Mr. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna (No. 149 with black crayon mark: "void."), 1957 Apr; 153; 1 blueline diazo print; 20 x 25 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Plan - alterations for Mr. & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna (No. 149 with additional electrical information notes in red pencil and with black crayon mark: "void."), 1957 Apr; 154; 1 blueline diazo print; 20 x 25 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Sheet 3 - furniture: alterations for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, incl. master bedroom, bath and library built-in details, 1957 Apr; 156; 1 blueline diazo print; 18 x 24 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Plot plan: house for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, showing preliminary design for new driveway and entrance retaining walls, handwritten note by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1957?; 159; 2 blueline diazo print; 30 x 36" (Box Sa20)
  - Plot Plan: House for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna; (Version of 156 [?160] with notes by David Dodge, apparently used as a job copy.), 1957 ?; 161; 1 blueline diazo print; 30 x 36 inches
  - Detail of entrance drive, showing brick retaining walls (with retaining wall section and elevation drawn in pencil), 162; 1 blueline diazo print; 16 x 41 inches (Box Sb15)
  - Entrance driveway and retaining wall layout, 1958 May 9; 163; 1 blackline diazo print; 16 x 40 inches (Box Sb15)
  - Roof plan for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, signed by William Wesley Peters, 1960 Jan 22; 164; 1 blueline diazo print; 35 x 42 inches (Box Sa17)
    Peters, William Wesley
  - Roof plan for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna; (No. 160 [?164] revised), 1960 Apr 28; 165; 1 blueline diazo print; 36 x 42 inches
  - Roof plan for Dr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna; (No. 161 [?165] with notes in pencil and ink.), 166; 1 blueline diazo print; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sa15)
  - Untitled, undated topographical survey of hill garden area, 167; 1 ink on tracing film; 21 x 36 inches
  - Details of shelter, undated drawing by Taliesin Associated Architects of summer house, 1961; 168; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 30 inches (Box Sb15)
    Taliesin Associated Architects
  - Details of shelter (No. 168 with field notes in pencil by Aaron Green), 1961; 169; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 30 inches (Box Sa14)
    Taliesin Associated Architects; Green, Aaron
  - Details of shelter (Revised edition of No. 168, by Aaron Green), 1961 Apr 26; 170; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 30 inches (Box Sa14)
  - Clarification drawing #1 (No. 171 with pencil field notes by Aaron Green.), 1961; 172; 1 blueline diazo print; 23 x 30 inches (Box Sa14)
    Green, Aaron
  - Clarification drawing #1 (This is a subsequent edition of No. 171.), 1961; 173; 1 blueline diazo print; 23 x 30 inches (Box Sa15)
  - Clarification drawing #1 (No. 171 with pencil field notes by Aaron Green.), 1961; 174; 2 blueline diazo print; 23 x 30 inches (Box Sa15)
  - Details of terrace chess tables, undated, 1961; 175; 2 blueline diazo print; 23 x 36 inches (Box Sb15, Sa15)
  - Details of terrace chess tables, undated; (Copy of No. 175 with red pencil notes), 1961; 176; 1 blueline diazo print; 23 x 36 inches (Box Sa15)
  - Floor plan - caretakers' apartment, showing proposed remodelling of Hobby Shop and Guest Room, dated June 30, 1974, 177; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 36 inches (Box Sb15)
  - View of study and dining area, perspective view of proposed remodelling of Hobby Shop, dated June 30, 1974, 178; 1 not given; not given (Box Sb15)
  - Sheet No. 1, plan & section: caretakers' apartment, dated August 1974; (in mylar folder with No. 180, 181, 182), 179; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 36 inches
  - Sections (unnumbered sheet): caretakers' apartment; (in mylar folder with No. 179, 181, 182), 1974 Aug; 180; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 36 inches
  - Study for powder room and mech. room, dated; (in mylar folder with No. 179, 180, 182), 1974 Oct; 181; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 36 inches
  - Plumbing plan: caretakers' apartment, dated; (in mylar folder with No. 179, 180, 181), 1974 Oct; 182; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 36 inches
  - Hobby shop - guest house remodel to caretaker apartment and guest house, signed J. S. Hanna and dated, 1980 May 5; 183; 1 pencil on tracing paper; 16 x 22 inches
  - Fence repair details for forecourt fence, initialled WJS and dated, 1980 May 30; 184; 1 blueline diazo print; 24 x 36 inches (Box Sb15)
  - Alterations for caretakers' apartment, 1982; 5 diazo prints ?
    Clark, Stromquist, and Sandstrom
  - Original topography of Hanna House site, 1936; 1 Ink on linen
  - Revised plan for concrete mat and brickwork (later edition of No. 7), 1936 ?; 8; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches
  - Floor plan (No. 9 with pencil and ink notations added by Hannas concerning electrical requirements.), 1936?; 10; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches
  - Floor plan, revised to show lighting and section lines (Subsequent edition of No. 9.), 1936 Dec 2; 11; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb17)
  - Exterior elevations (3) and section A-A, initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1936 Nov 11; 18; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches
  - Revised southeast and northwest elevations, dated and initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1937 Jan 30; 21; 1 blueprint; 23.5 x 42 inches
  - Revised, exterior elevations (3), section A-A and section B-B (subsequent edition of No. 18), 1936 Dec 7; 23; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches
  - Section E-E thru entrance loggia and section G-G thru bedroom, bathroom and playroom, ilitialled and dated by Frank Lloyd Wright (date illeg - 1937) (sections are mislabelled: E-E should read C-C and G-G should read E-E to agree with No. 30), 34; 1 blueprint; 31.5 x 42 inches
  - Full size detail of flat roof fascia over folding sash, incl. dimensions of wall plate, initialled and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 46; 1 blueprint; 28 x 42 inches
  - Details for easy chair and tabourette, initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1946 Sep 20; 87; 1 blueprint; 28 x 29 inches (Box Sb11)
  - Addition and alterations to 'Honeycomb' House..., showing floor plan and elevations of revised scheme for addition of guest room and hobby shop, 1948; 91; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches
  - Addition and alterations to 'Honeycomb' House..., showing floor plan and elevations of revised scheme for addition of guest room and hobby shop (same as No. 91 with notes in pencil), 1948; 92; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches
  - Contour detail - front drive, Hanna residence, undated; 158; 1 ink on tracing film; 18.5 x 48 inches
  - Proposed steps [to terrace]; initialled by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1957; 1 Pencil on tracing paper; 17.75 x 12.5 inches
  - Detail of entrance drive, undated; 3 Diazo prints; 16.25 x 40.5 inches
    Detail of entrance drive; Detail of entrance drive with additional sketches of brick walls; Reverse image of second drawing
  - Plot plan, revised to show sewage and drainage; mark-ups by Jean Hanna, showing entrance retaining walls., 1936 Dec 2, 1957; 6; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Roof plan, initialled and dated by Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1936 Nov 11; 24; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Sections and interior elevations, undated; 22; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Revised elevations (subsequent edition of no. 19), undated; 20; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Topographic survey of Hanna lot, 1936; 4; 1 blueprint; 42 x 36.5 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Full size details, initialled and dated (illegible) by Wright, Frank Lloyd; (Wall and sash details; flat roof eave detail; wall and sash corner details.), 26; 1 blueprint; 36 x 42 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Revised roof plan (subsequent edition of No. 24), 25; 1 blueprint; 34.5 x 42 inches (Box Sb16)
  - Revised full size details (subsequent edition of No. 26), 27; 1 blueprint; 38 x 42 inches
  - Entrance lantern, incl. plan at three levels and cross section, 48; 1 blueprint; 38 x 40.5 inches
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna; elevation from the south, circa 1936; AD001; 1 diazo print; 40.5 x 17 inches (Box Sb18)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna; elevation from entrance side, circa 1936; AD002; 1 diazo print; 40 x 17 inches (Box Sb18)
  - [Hanna House as drawn for article in House Beautiful; with notes], 1962; 1 blueprint
  - Dwelling for Dr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna. House Beautiful Magazine Stage 3; with note from Gair Sloan. (dwg is folded inside mylar), 1963 Sep 23; 1 (Box Sb11)
  - Dwelling for Dr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna. House Beautiful Magazine Stage 3; with note to Miss Gordon from Gair Sloan., 1963 Sep 23; 1 (Box Sa19)
  - Dwelling for Dr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna. House Beautiful Magazine Stage 2; with note to the Hanna's from Gair Sloan., 1962 Sep 17; 1 (Box Sa19)
  - Dwelling for Dr. & Mrs. Paul Hanna. House Beautiful Magazine Revised Stage 1; with note to the Hanna's from Gair Sloan., 1962 Sep 19; AD007; 1 (Box Sa19)
  - Revised floor plan (1st. revision noted on reverse), [1937]; AD004 (Box Sa20)
  - Chimney details, section A, section B (plus various plan views of chimney), 40; 1 diazo; 43 x 16 in. (approx.) (Box Sb12)
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb" House for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, CA, undated; sc0280_001; blueprints (reprographic copies); 36 x 42 inches
  - Section A–A, Sash folding on track, Hanna House, intialled and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, undated; sc0280_002; blueprints (reprographic copies); 34.5 x 42 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "54; detail of sash folding on track; copy 2"
  - Full size detail of clerestory windows, Hanna House, intialled and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, undated; sc0280_003; blueprints (reprographic copies); 31 x 36 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "61; details of clerestory windows"
  - Furniture sheet No. 3, Hanna House, intialled and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, undated; sc0280_004; blueprints (reprographic copies); 33 x 42 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "Sheet 3; 103; details of furniture in study and bedroom"
  - Details showing use of outside sash with the jamb, Sash sheet No. 2, Hanna House, intialled and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, undated; sc0280_005; blueprints (reprographic copies); 34 x 36 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "Duplicates"
  - Framing plan for pitched roofs, Hanna House, intialled and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, undated; sc0280_006; blueprints (reprographic copies); 36 x 35 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "6; Framing plan for pitched roof"
  - Addition to the residence of Professor & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer & WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 1, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_01; blueprints (reprographic copies); 29.5 x 41.5 inches
    Originally bound with 5 other drawings
  - Addition to the residence of Professor & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer & WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 2, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_02; blueprints (reprographic copies); 29.5 x 41.5 inches
  - Addition to the residence of Professor & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer & WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 3, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_03; blueprints (reprographic copies); 29.5 x 41.5 inches